<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="template.xsl"?>
<root>
    
    <image>images/banners/ptitle.jpg</image>
	<bgcolor>#052F59</bgcolor>
	<cbgcolor>#999</cbgcolor>
	<sbgcolor>#999</sbgcolor>
	<abgcolor>#999</abgcolor>
	<lbgcolor>#999</lbgcolor>
	<color>#052F59</color>
   <pagelinks>
   		<pl>
			<text value='current'>About Us</text>
			
			<linkto>navpages/aboutus.xml</linkto>
		</pl>
		<pl>
			<text>About San Antonio</text>
			
			<linkto>navpages/aboutsan.xml</linkto>
		</pl>
		<pl>
			<text>Organizations</text>
			
			<linkto>navpages/organization.xml</linkto>
		</pl>
		<pl>
			<text>Contact Us</text>
			
			<linkto>navpages/contactus.xml</linkto>
		</pl>
		<pl>
			<text>FAQ's</text>
			<linkto>navpages/faq.xml</linkto>
		</pl>
   </pagelinks>
    <bodytext>
		<p>
		<h3>Message from the Executive Director:</h3>
      	<p>Welcome to the web site of International Student Services and Admissions office at Central University.</p>
			<p>We are proud of the diversity of our international students, faculty, and staff who represent over 44 countries from around the world. Central
					University highly values our international community and is deeply committed to its support and growth.</p>
			<p>We are proud of the diversity of our international students, faculty, and staff who represent over 44 countries from around the world. Central 
			University highly values our international community and is deeply committed to its support and growth.</p>
			<p>The greatest numbers of our international students come to study Engineering, Computer Science, Business, or Nursing. Increasingly however, 
			we see growing interest and admissions for study in Kinesiology, Audiology, Education and Human Development and many other departments.</p>
			<p>However you shape your academic goals, International Student Services and Admissions office is dedicated to providing exemplary service and support to our 
			international community.</p>
			<p>We work hard to ensure that the time you spend at Central is productive as well as interesting, generating quality experiences which will serve you and enrich you 
			the rest of your life.</p>
			<p>We actively engage international students by providing the information and resources about US laws and regulations, helping you develop leadership skills for the 
			global marketplace, and when you need it, providing care and help for your own very personal concerns.</p>
			<p>International Student Services and Admissions is also home to Central Language Institute. LLI offers intensive English language training to individuals who want to 
			improve English language skills in preparation for admission to Central or any other university where English is the primary medium of instruction.</p>
			<p>We vigorously promote cultural education throughout the university. A wide range of educational options and events provide a healthy medium for cultural exchange 
			and appreciation. In short, we are here not only to serve international students but also as a resource to the University, as advocates for global awareness, cultural 
			competency, and a catalyst for positive change.</p>
			<p>I am confident that our web site contains the very information you need for success as student at Central University. We constantly try to present all the necessary
		 that an international student needs to know. If you don't find what you need here, please e-mail me at surya.gade@central.edu. Or call our office at (210) 880-2264.</p>
		 <p>We welcome you to Central University where we look forward to helping you build a great future.</p>
		
		<p style="color:#000;">
			Yours Sincerely, <br />
			Dr. John Doe <br />
			Executive Director ,<br />
			International Student Services and Admissions,<br />
			Central University.<br />
		</p>
		</p>
		
    </bodytext>
  
</root>

